Smile, you still followin' Peco wherever he goes?
（アクマ）スマイル
まだペコに 金魚のフンみてえに
くっついてんのかよ
タムラのオババに よろしくな
Say hi to the old lady for me.
（スマイル）すごいな アクマ
海王(かいおう)の先鋒(せんぽう)だって
Demon's amazing. He's playing the first game for Kaiou.
Could you ask him to come to our school?
（ドラゴン）何とか月本(つきもと)君を
うちに呼べないものかな
（アクマ）えい
絶対 負けない
唯一の方法はだな—
The only way to be sure you won't lose is to not fight.
闘わないことだ
風間(かざま)先輩は どこでありますか？
Where's Kazama?
A new age has dawned, and still I can't make a decision
My path is too straight for my taste, but I'll walk it
I can't choose just yet
I have to think about it
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm going crazy!
Comparing yourself to others just makes you depressed
You're alone in this world
You're always alone here
Still you're gonna do it, right?
Maybe there's nothing that only I can do
But there's no way that I
But there's no way that I won't try to leave my mark
I just want to have my fun, whatever the times
You sure, Wenge?
You don't have to stay here alone.
Kong Wenge (China)
Right-Chinese
Penhold Grip
Pips-In Rubber
on Both Sides
Style:
Counter Driver
Interhigh
Preliminaries
Quarterfinalist
Kong Wenge (China)
Right-Chinese
Penhold Grip
Pips-In Rubber
on Both Sides
Style:
Counter Driver
Interhigh
Preliminaries
Quarterfinalist
Well, I don't know how I can face them...
Plus, I was hired to beef up that week little club,
even if that wasn't the real goal.
Hello. Goodbye. Thank you.
（チャイナ）
コンニチワ　サヨウナラ
アリガトウゴザイマス
Heh heh. Pretty good, huh?
The only saving grace is that Kazama won worlds as well.
If he'd lost the Interhigh,
I would've found a witch to turn me into a frog.
I'll miss you, Wenge.
Right back at ya.
Kazama! Congratulations on your gold
medal in singles at the Youth Olympics!
風間君 ユースオリンピック
シングルス 優勝おめでとう
何か感想を
Could you share your thoughts?
My performance in the team and
doubles events was less than stellar,
（ドラゴン）団体ダブルスでは
いまひとつでしたが—
シングルスでの優勝には
満足しています
but I'm satisfied with my victory in the singles.
Kazama
Ryuuichi
(Dragon)
Kaiou Captain
Right
Shakehand
Grip
Style:
All-rounder
Youth
Olympics
Gold
Medalist
Kazama
Ryuuichi
(Dragon)
Kaiou Captain
Right
Shakehand
Grip
Style:
All-rounder
Youth
Olympics
Gold
Medalist
From Narita Airport
Table Tennis Youth
Olympics Gold Medalist
However, what I'm most worried about is my school, Kaiou.
しかし 私が
いちばん憂えているのは—
我が母校 海王のことであります
From Narita Airport
Table Tennis Youth
Olympics Gold Medalist
The overall strength of our team has dropped.
今 チーム全体の総合力は
確実に低下しており—
For Kaiou Academy to be as formidable as it once was,
今後 我々 海王学園高校が
以前のように盤石を誇るには—
we require players as good as
Tsukimoto from Katase High School.
片瀬(かたせ)高校の
月本選手レベルのプレーヤーが—
必要不可欠です
Kazama!
（記者）風間君！
Huh?
（記者）あれ もう？
That's it?
Huh? Is that the girl from the commercials?
（記者）あれ？ ＣＭの彼女？
（記者）ポセイドンの？
The ones for Poseidon?
That was an all-too-brief interview with Kazama Ryuuichi,
who took singles gold in the Youth Olympics table tennis.
（リポーター）
あっという間でしたが
ユースオリンピック シングルス
優勝の風間竜一(りゅういち)君でした
Now, back to you.
こちらからは以上です
From Narita Airport
Table Tennis Youth
Olympics Gold Medalist
From Narita Airport
Table Tennis Youth
Olympics Gold Medalist
（百合枝(ゆりえ)）卓球しようよ
Let's play table tennis!
For all your table tennis needs.
Poseidon
藤沢駅前
By Fujisawa Station.
Congrats! You're amazing, Ryuu!
おめでとう　竜(りゅう)ちゃん すごいね
Auntie Emiko was overjoyed too.
えみ子(こ)おばちゃんも
すっごい喜んでた
連絡した？
Have you called her?
いや
No.
You should! She'd be really happy.
してあげなよ すごい喜ぶ
I hear she always shows her customers newspaper clippings of you.
お客さんに いつも竜ちゃんの
切り抜き 見せてんだって
おうち？
So, home?
No. I want to see the old man first.
いや まず じじに挨拶したい
Really? That sucks.
そっかあ 大変
近くに おいしいパンケーキの店が
あるんだけど
Say, there's a good pancake house nearby...
Sorry. I get it.
ごめん　分かった
Even though you're world champ, you've got it rough.
竜ちゃん
世界一になったのに大変ね
世界の中心に
おじじがいるみたい
It's like Grampa's at the center of the world!
yen
Parasol
Beach Chair
Mat
Inflatable Raft
Banana Boat
yen
That's pricey.
（ペコ）高っ
yen
It's dirt cheap.
（女子）全然 安いよ
リゾートビーチ行ったら
倍以上するよ
You'd pay more than double this at a resort beach!
You sure we need these?
（ペコ）いらなくね？
We'd burn to a crisp in less than half an hour without a parasol.
（女子）パラソルなしじゃ
30分で黒焦げになっちゃうよ
And chairs are mandatory!
チェアも絶対ね
もう 砂まみれになっちゃうよ
Jeez, I'm gonna be covered in sand!
Table Tennis News
We have a World Juniors Winner!
Rub lotion on me.
（女子）ねえ クリーム塗って
（ペコ）ちょっと待て
Gimme a minute.
（女子）
何それ 超ウケる
What's up with that? It's hilarious.
すごい
ひび入ってんだけど
It's totally cracked.
from Katase High School
For Kaiou Academy
to be as formidable as it once was
we require players as good as Tsukimoto
from Katase High School
Huh?
Tsukimoto
Hey, isn't there a famous pancake house around here?
（女子）ねえ この近くにさ
有名なパンケーキの店あるよね
にいちゃん こっち！
Yo, we want to order.
（江上(えがみ)）あっ はい
Yes, sir.
（ペコ）注文 お願い
Order something for me.
What?
What would you like?
何にしましょう？
I don't want that crap.
（女子）いらないわよ
What?
Oh...
I guess the beach isn't right for me, either.
どうにも
海にも水が合わねえってか
山 行ってみるか
Maybe I'll try the mountains.
イッヒヒ
（店員）ハア…
そろそろ時間なんで いいっすか？
Are you ready?
We're about to close up.
Good work, Ryuuichi.
（風間理事長）よくやった 竜一
Next we'll spend some money
on a commercial featuring you.
次は お前で
金かけてＣＭを撮ろう
Still, you pulled quite the stunt!
しかし ずいぶんな
ふりだったじゃないか
And on TV too.
テレビでやるとはな
Will he come to us?
そいつは うちに来るのか？
No doubt.
（ドラゴン）必ず
I'm sure he knows where he belongs.
彼は自分にふさわしい場所を
知っているはずです
I'm counting on you.
頼むぞ
海王は常勝でなければならん
Kaiou must always win.
This isn't good, Ryuuichi.
（卓(たく)）マズいな 竜一
You know it isn't.
マズいだろう
（ドラゴン）押忍(おす)！
申し訳ありません！
Yes, sir!
I'm very sorry, sir!
お前がホントに 海王のことを
憂えてるのは分かんだけど—
I can tell you're genuinely worried for Kaiou.
Kazama Ryuuichi
Fails to Defend Title
But the guys who got crushed at the Interhigh haven't bounced back yet,
インハイで ぼろ負けした連中は
まだ立ち直っちゃいねえんだし—
Kaiou Academy sinks
Defeated in the second
round of the team event
and their captain only caring about another school's player is a slap in the face.
キャプテンが他校の選手ばかり
気にしているってのは どうなんだ
Kazama Ryuuichi
Fails to Defend Title
Second Consecutive
Individual Victory
（ドラゴン）申し訳ありません！
My apologies, sir!
Yo. I hear Kazama got called into the Coach's office.
（真田(さなだ)）よう
風間は呼び出しば食ろうとっとね
（部員）うっす
（部員）押忍！
Yes, sir!
He ran his mouth at the airport on the afternoon news.
昼間のテレビね
空港でしゃべっちょった
はい
Yes, sir.
Apparently, the guy's like a robot. He doesn't even smile.
（猫田(ねこた)）
ロボットみたいなやつらしいで
ニコリとも せえへんて
His name's Tsukimoto, right?
月本 言いよったか？
But we're talking about Kazama here.
ともあれ 風間のことやけん—
うかつに
口滑らせよったわけじゃなかろうね
He didn't mention him by accident.
本気で その七三メガネば
うちに引き込む腹ばい
He's planning to get that four-eyes with the parted hair on our team.
（猫田）せやろな
Probably so.
Sakuma Manabu (Demon)
Right Penhold Grip
Pips-In/Long
Pips-Out
Style: Modern
Defender
Defeated in
Interhigh,
Second Round
Sakuma Manabu (Demon)
Right Penhold Grip
Pips-In/Long
Pips-Out
Style: Modern
Defender
Defeated in
Interhigh,
Second Round
Where Did I
Go Wrong?
（チャイナ）
アリガトウ　ゴクロウサマ
Thanks. Good work.
Your speed is dropping.
（小泉(こいずみ)）落ちてるよ ピッチ
Pick it up!
上げて 上げて
腕振る！ もっと もっと！
Swing your arms.
More! More!
Tough it out!
耐える！
There!
そこで！
はい オーケー！
Okay, you're good.
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Tsukimoto Makoto
(Smile)
Right
Shakehand
Grip
Pips-In/
Long Pips-Out
Style:
Attacking
Chopper
Defeated in
Interhigh, Third Round
Tsukimoto Makoto
(Smile)
Right
Shakehand
Grip
Pips-In/
Long Pips-Out
Style:
Attacking
Chopper
Defeated in
Interhigh, Third Round
Don't stop.
止まるな 止まるな
Keep walking.
歩いて 歩いて
Hey, Captain Oota.
ヘーイ キャプテン大田(おおた)
ご帰宅かね？
You heading home?
（大田）うーっす
Yes, sir.
We're calling it a day, but do
you need help with anything?
俺ら上がりますけど
何か手伝うことあります？
No, thanks.
ないよ　サンクス
（大田）それじゃ 失礼しまーす
See you later, then!
Goodbye.
（小泉）グッバーイ
ちぇっ 何だかなあ
I don't like it.
（高村(たかむら)）大田 今日は？
Oota, what're you up to today?
Getting my license.
免許だ 免許
うちの軽トラ
運転しなきゃいけねえから
Gotta be able to drive my family's light truck.
家業か　いいなあ
A family business must be nice.
We're college-bound with no prospects.
俺たち 当てのない受験生
Moron.
バーカ
おめえは町の小さな家電屋の
大変さを知らねえ
You don't know how rough small-town appliance stores have it.
Your bowl-headed friend didn't come today, either.
今日も例のおかっぱ 来とらんね
Let's go inside.
（スマイル）
入りましょう　体 冷えますよ
We'll catch a chill.
Hm? Ah, right.
（小泉）
うーん ああそうか うん
（スマイル）次は多球練習です
Next is multi-ball training.
Okay.
（小泉）オーケー
（小泉）足使う 足！
Use your feet.
ほら 浮いてる 球が
You missed a ball.
手だけで返すな
Don't return with just your hands.
遅い 遅い！
バタついてんだよ 足が！
You're slow! Too slow! Your feet are flopping all over the place!
Personally, I like Akagi Dairy.
赤城(あかぎ)乳業 好きよ 俺
個人的にね
I'm impressed by their liberal management style.
自由な経営スタイルが
好感持てる
BLACKのＣＭも
シャレてるしね
Their BLACK commercials are pretty sharp too.
The success of their cream products hasn't made them arrogant.
クリーム系でヒット飛ばしても
慢心せず—
They keep putting out new products.
どんどん新作 出してくるあたり
さすが
真っ黒だな　誰かと思ったぜ
You look like burnt toast.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I thought you quit, Hoshino.
やめたんじゃねえのか？ 星野(ほしの)
I don't see Smile around.
スマイル いないのね
少し太ったか？ お前
Have you put on weight?
Ugh, for real?!
（ペコ）げっ ウソ！
Tsukimoto's running laps outside with the old man.
（大田）月本なら
じいさんと一緒に外周 行ったぜ
He's on a completely different training regimen from us.
何しろ やつは
俺らと完全に別メニューで動いてる
He comes to school at five in the morning and runs ten kilometers.
朝５時から学校 来て
10キロ走んだよ 10キロ
He's doing three times the exercise we are.
運動量だけで 俺らの３倍はある
The old man arranges a stupid
number of matches for him too.
試合の数だって
じいさんが—
バカみてえに
半端なく組んじまう
（ペコ）なんで？
Why?
Hello, everybody.
ハロー エブリバディ
集合したかね？
Are you all here?
メッス！
Yo.
少し太った？
Have you put on weight?
買い替えたメガネのせいで
そう映るのよ
Your new glasses just make it look that way.
（スマイル）お菓子の食べすぎ
You've been eating too many sweets.
俺のポリシーだ
That's my policy.
（スマイル）タバコも？
（ペコ）え？
The cigarettes too?
Huh?
見下げてんのな 俺らのことを
He looks down on us.
He plays so many matches because
none of us are worth practicing with.
バカみてえに試合するのも—
うちに
ろくな練習相手がいねえからさ
Which means we play schools that're at his level.
（部員）おかげで俺らは—
やつのレベルに合った学校と
打ち合うわけで
王子様は お一人で
連勝街道を突っ走っておいでだがな
The prince rides the winning-streak highway alone.
There's no "team" here anymore.
もう この部に
チームなんて存在しねえ
He's the only member of the first string; everyone else is just a ball boy.
やつ１人が一軍で
他は球拾いって図式よ
What? Sakuma's not here?
何や？ 佐久間(さくま)が来よらんてな？
押忍！ 風邪気味じゃけ
寮にて静養する言うとりました！
No, sir! He said he'd rest up in the dorms because he's coming down with a cold!
風邪で？
A cold?
Very well.
分かった
ああ もうよか　行きんしゃい
Fine. You can go.
（部員たち）押忍！
Yes, sir!
Three!
（部員たち）３！
（部員たち）４！
Four!
Look, I don't believe in Sakuma's "cold."
佐久間の風邪じゃが
わしゃ 信じとらんけんね
One!
Two!
He's the type who'd play with appendicitis.
あれは盲腸 腫らしてん
ラケット振る男たい
Three!
Four!
The posters in his dorm room ain't funny to me.
Tsuburaya
やつが部屋に貼っとう
ポスターば わしは笑えん
He worships you like a god.
やつは貴様(きさん)のことば
神様のごつ崇拝しとう
One, two, three, four!
Where would a guy like that go?
そげんやつが
どこへ出向きよったか
Kaiou doesn't tolerate us playin' other schools' athletes without permission.
うちは勝手ん対外試合ば
やることば—
One, two, three, four!
厳しく禁じちょう
Knowing that, where could Sakuma have gone?
それ知っちょって なお
佐久間が どこぞ行きよったか
貴様(きさん)が片高(かたこう)の月本とかいうカットば
欲しがるのは かまわん
It's fine by me if you want that chopper from Katase.
One, two, three, four!
But it seems to me that if you go around callin' us losers in public,
ばってん—
わしらんこと用なしのごと
吹いて回りよっとると—
it might throw a spanner in the works.
まとまるもんも
まとまらんとやないか？
One, two, three, four!
（部員たち）１　２…
のう 風間よ
You hear me, Kazama?
風間  休憩 終わっちょるばい
Kazama, break time is over.
Oh.
Concerned about Sakuma after all, huh?
（真田）やっぱ あれか
佐久間んこと
気になりようとやろ？
（ドラゴン）いや…
No.
そやね あの佐久間に限って…
Yeah, Sakuma's the last guy who'd—
佐久間は負ける
Sakuma will lose.
Tsukimoto Makoto's play is on a
different level from the rest of you.
月本 誠(まこと)は—
すでに君らとは違う段階の卓球を
身につけているよ
Sakuma can't beat him.
あれは負ける
キンモクセイの香りがするね
I smell sweet olive.
Excuse me, but we need to start!
（大野(おおの)）先輩！ そろそろ…
Yeah, yeah, we're comin'!
（真田）おう！
今 行きよろうが
Anyway, Sakuma will leave a hole in our team.
とにかく
佐久間の抜けた穴…
What?
Our most pressing need is finding someone to fill it.
その人材を見つけることこそ
我々の急務だよ
You hold it right there.
ちょっと待たんかい コラァ
そげん話 聞いて 佐久間が
どげん思えばしよろうかのう
How do you figure Sakuma'd feel if he heard that? Well?
He's been with us through thick and thin!
わしらと苦楽ば共にしてきよった
佐久間がのう
その憐憫(れんびん)が—
Here's what I'd like to know: how is that compassion going to help us regain our former glory?
我が海王卓球部の
名門復活に—
どう役立つのかと
問いたい
We can't even dominate the Interhigh without
players who can win on the international stage.
世界で勝てるプレーヤー
でなければ—
インハイをも
制することはできない
Nothing has changed. We're still in crisis.
旧態依然　危急存亡
じき 冬が来る
Winter is coming.
Smells like trouble.
何か大変そうね
面白がってるだろう
You think it's funny, don't you?
Is it about what Ryuu said on TV?
（百合枝）
竜ちゃんがテレビで言ったこと？
Yeah.
うん まあ…
Thanks.
ありがとう
There's a first-year on my team. One of a dying breed.
今どき珍しい子が
１年坊にいるんだ
He plays our first match.
先鋒をやってる子なんだが
上手なの？
Is he good?
He's the poster boy for awkwardness. If there were contests in it, he'd be in the running immediately.
不器用さを絵に描きゃ—
即 コンクールで
入選するってタイプの男だ
スカウトしたわけじゃなく—
I didn't scout him.
In fact, I was set against letting him on the team.
むしろ入部させることすら
強く反対した
君が苦しむことになるからと
さんざん断ったが—
I kept turning him down, telling him he'd only suffer.
But he refused to listen. He said,
"I came to Kaiou to become like Kazama."
“風間先輩のようになりたくて
海王に来たのだ”と—
頑として聞かん
いずれは
マネージャーにでもと思って—
I caved, figuring I could make him
manager someday... But you know what?
しぶしぶ取ったんだが
こいつが—
He turned out to be the type who, if you tell him to
drop and give you ten, will do a hundred or a thousand.
十やれと言えば
百でも千でも続けるような男だった
But table tennis is a sport where natural talent really matters.
しかし卓球は
素質が大きく ものいう競技だ
It's impossible for him to become like Ryuuichi.
竜一を目指すには
無理がありすぎる
But your dad here likes him.
でも父さん そいつが好きでな
かわいくて しかたなかったよ
ホント
He's just too adorable for me!
It's the same for our team now.
今のチームにしても同じだ
We're weaker than we were in our glory days, but I love those guys.
確かに全盛期と比べれば
戦力は劣るが—
俺は愛している
I wish Ryuuichi felt the same way.
できれば竜一にも—
同じ気持ちで
あってほしいんだが
It's not easy when things don't go your way.
なかなか難しいね
思ったとおりにいかないなんて
What will you do when you graduate from junior college?
お前 短大出たら
どうするんだ？
うーん 考えてる
I'm thinking it over.
Let me hear you, first-years!
オラァ！ 声出せ １年！
Yes, sir!
あらら
Oh dear.
Hey. What's wrong, mister?
（小泉）
ヘーイ どうした？ ミスター
なぜ止める　カモーン
Why did you stop? Come on!
Come on, Demon.
（ペコ）おいおい アクマ
お前さんの乱視は
そこまで進行してんのか？
Have your eyes gotten that bad?
You got off at the wrong station.
駅 間違えてんよ
This isn't Kaiou Academy, you know.
ここは はいほうはふへん…
ヘヘヘ 少し太ったか？ ペコ
Put on some weight, Peco?
（ペコ）イッテ…
失礼します！
監督さんは どちらにおられますか
Excuse me!
Where might I find the coach?
（小泉）ヒア
Here.
Sir!
押忍！
自分は海王１年
佐久間であります！
I am Sakuma, first-year at Kaiou!
I've come here today because I'd like to play Tsukimoto!
本日は 月本選手と
試合させていただきたく—
参上しました！
You heard him.
ってさ
やってもいいけど アクマ
I don't mind playing, Demon.
But you'll lose.
お前 負けるよ
Aren't you cool?
カッコいいー！
Whatever. I don't care anymore.
（大田）何でもやってくれよ もう
（小泉）試合をするのは
かまわないが—
I don't mind you playing a match,
君の学校は 個人的な対外試合を
禁止していなかったかね？
but doesn't Kaiou forbid playing
other schools without permission?
ええ 負けでもしたら
即 退部になります
Yes. If we lose, we're kicked off the team immediately.
Did you hear that, mister?
聞いたか ミスター
新撰組(しんせんぐみ)みたいよ
They're like the Shinsengumi.
近藤(こんどう) 勇(いさみ)も許可してないのかね？
You don't have Kondou Isami's permission?
I didn't even tell Hijikata I was coming.
土方(ひじかた)にも告げずに来ましたよ
So you're prepared to commit ritual suicide.
切腹覚悟というわけだ
Okay, Mr. Okita.
オッケー ミスター沖田(おきた)
We'll gift you some of our time.
我々の時間を少し
君にプレゼントするよ
15分で済ませてくれ
Wrap it up in fifteen minutes.
I want to finish up the rest of our regimen.
残りのメニューも消化したい
Got it.
分かりました
Bring it on.
上等
It's been two years and four
months since I played you, Smile.
（アクマ）
お前と打つのは２年４か月ぶりだな
スマイル
（スマイル）そうだっけ？
Has it?
（主審）タイム！
Time!
My record against you is 96 - 37.
俺の96勝37敗さ
（スマイル）そんなこと忘れたよ
I don't remember any of that.
Ready!
（主審）レディー！
（アクマ）ちっとばっか—
Don't get ahead of yourself just
because Kazama likes you a little bit.
風間さんに気に入られてっからって
調子くれんな
お前の連勝記録も—
Your winning streak comes from playing easy games against rank amateurs.
しょせん 止めマン相手の
あそ卓にすぎねえよ
井の中の蛙(かわず)が水遊び…
You're just a big fish in a small pond.
いくよ
Here we go.
ワンラブ！
One-love!
I can see you've improved a little, Smile.
（アクマ）ちったあ成長の跡が
見られるじゃねえの スマイル君よ
That guy's not bad. He returned Tsukimoto's third shot!
やるな あいつ
月本の３球目 返したよ
That's Kaiou for you.
やっぱ海王は違うな
（アクマ）ちっ
（主審）ラブツー
Love-two!
Love-three!
（主審）ラブスリー
Four-love!
フォーラブ
イレブンワン　ゲーム トゥ 月本
Eleven-one!
Game goes to Tsukimoto!
Smile, you bastard...
スマイル てめえ
（子供のアクマ）
あんな単純な回転に
引っ掛かんなよ
Don't be fooled by simple spin like that.
ボケ
Moron.
（子供のペコ）
うぉーい アクマやい
Hey, Demon.
Don't hit Smile.
スマイル たたくなよ
But, Peco... this guy sucks.
でもよ ペコ
こいつってば 全然ダメなの
He doesn't get any better.
まるで うまくならねえんだよ
The right?
（アクマの声）右？
アウト！
Out!
（アクマ）いやあ！
Two-eleven!
ツーイレブン　ゲーム トゥ 月本
Game goes to Tsukimoto.
Damn it.
（アクマの声）チクショウ
まるっきり球種が読めねえ
I can't predict his shots at all.
揺さぶりも効かねえ
I can't throw him off, either.
He returns my knuckleballs with ease.
ナックルも平気で拾う
Tsukimoto up two games to love!
（主審）
ゲームカウント ツーゼロ　月本
（アクマの声）
まるで大学生か社会人と
打ってるみてえだ
I feel like I'm playing a college student or a pro.
Where did I go wrong?
いったい どこで間違えた？
（アクマの声）
いったい 何に つまずいた？
What tripped me up?!
That's some astigmatism you've got, Manabu.
ひどい乱視だね 学(まなぶ)君
（アクマの声）どこで間違えた？
Where did I go wrong?
これからは
目が疲れたら遠くを見るよう
Focus on distant objects when your eyes get tired.
What tripped me up?!
（アクマの声）何に つまずいた？
この子は私と違って目がいいんだ
Unlike me, he's got good eyes.
Look at that, Manabu.
ほら 学 あれをご覧
違うよ 学 あれはポッポだよ
No, Manabu.
That's a choo-choo, not a vroom-vroom.
ブーブとは違う
（アクマの声）どこで間違えた？
Where did I go wrong?
Once I'm out of high school, I'm going to Europe.
俺 高校ハネったら
ヨーロッパ行く構えよ
Sakuma's playing our first match?
おう 佐久間が先鋒か
I have high hopes for him.
期待してるぞ
（アクマの声）何に つまずいた？
What tripped me up?!
Come on, Manabu.
さあ 学
What...
そこから—
can you see?
何が…
Straight? No!
ストレート？ いや…
Five-love!
（主審）ファイブラブ！
Damn it!
チクショー！
Why you? Why?!
どうして お前なんだよ！
いったい どうして！
俺は努力したよ
I worked hard!
お前の10倍…
いや100倍 1,000倍したよ！
Ten! No, a hundred! A thousand times harder than you!
All so that Kazama would acknowledge my skill!
風間さんに認められるために
All so I could beat Peco!
ペコに勝つために！
From dawn until dusk, my only thoughts were of table tennis!
それこそ朝から晩まで
卓球のことだけを考えて—
卓球に すべてを捧(ささ)げてきたよ
I've given everything I had to table tennis!
なのに…
So why—
それは アクマに
卓球の才能がないからだよ
Because you haven't got a talent for table tennis, Demon.
単純に それだけのことだよ
That's all there is to it.
It's nothing to shout about.
大声で騒ぐほどのことじゃない
Bullshit.
ふざけんな
そんなことあるわけ…
That can't be...
試合 続ける気ないなら
帰ってほしい
If you're not going to keep playing, leave.
I don't have time for this.
僕も それほど暇じゃない
It can't be. That's not possible...
（アクマ）
そんな… そんなはず…
So, there are different theories about how Bruce Lee died—
（男性）ほいでさあ—
ブルース・リーの死因には
多説あってね
イッテえな
ガキが どこ見て歩いて…
That hurt, brat! Where are you looki—
うるせえ！
Shut up!
Kaiou Academy Table Tennis Team Member Sakuma Manabu
Where do I have to look for you to praise me, huh?!
（蹴る音）
（アクマ）どこ見て歩きゃあ—
褒めてくれんだよ
え？ おい！
Suspended from school for two weeks for causing bodily harm and...
Answer me! Come on!
答えてくれよ
オラァ！
何 見て歩きゃあよ！
Where should I look when I'm walking?!
removed from the table tennis team
悪(わり)いな 相棒
Sorry, partner.
Rest in peace, yeah?
成仏してくれよ
A red sun stares at me
The world goes blurry when I yawn
My wishes fluctuate like a metronome
Everything tells me this is the end
I do have some dreams, you know
Sometimes we breathe
and just seem to inhale the smoke of someone
somewhere out of sight
Then all our great energy just seems to melt away
I don't understand this wonderland
I won't get wet even if it rains
This is a wonderland
Once I've made it through this long tunnel
I'm sure that someone will kiss me